ILR School Founding Faculty Oral History Project /4135 OHT
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Founding Faculty Oral History Project
1989-1994
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Schatz, Ronald
/4135 OHT
9.67 cubic feet
9.7 linear ft.
Oral histories (document genres).
Audio recordings of interviews with the founding faculty of the ILR school
7587535
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 29, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 03, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4069: ILR School Founding Documents /4027 OHM: ILR History Interviews /4104 OHT: ILR School 40th Anniversary Interviews /4189 OH: ILR School External Relations Office Oral History Interviews
Aronson, Robert; Blumen, Isadore; Brooks, George; Clark, M. Gardner; Cook, Alice; Cullen, Donald; Donovan, Ronald; Gray, Lois; Hildebrand, George; Jensen, Vernon; Konvitz, Milton; McConnell, John; McIntyre, Duncan; McKelvey, John; Miller, J. Gormley; Neufeld, Maurice F.; Raimon, Robert L.; Schatz, Ronald; Whyte, William; Windmuller, John P.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
7587535
- Aronson (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Aronson (7/15/1991) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Blumen (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Brooks, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Scope and Contents
  review copy (8/20/1992)
- Clark, M.G. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Cook (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Cullen (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Donovan (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Gray, L. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Hildebrandt (9/26/1991) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Jensen (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Jensen (1990) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Convicts (Box 1, Folder 13)
- McConnell (Box 1, Folder 14)
- MacIntyre (Box 1, Folder 15)
- MacIntyre, Duncan, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Ronald Senate, Interviewer - 12 July 1991 - Rev. 1994
- McKelvey (Box 2, Folder 2)
- McKelvey (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Miller, J.G. (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Neufield, M. (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Neufield (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Ramon (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Whyte, Wm. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Windmuller (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Copies of signed memos & authorization sheets (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Memo of understanding (Box 2, Folder 11)
- ILR Oral History - Schatz (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Transcriber - Correspondence & discs (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Prof. Robert Aronson - tape #1 (7/10/1990) (Box 3.1)
  - Prof. Robert Aronson, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - tape #1-#2 (7/10/1990)
- Prof. Robert Aronson - tape #2 (7/10/1990) (Box 3.2)
- Prof. Robert Aronson - tape #1 (7/10/1990) (Box 3.3)
- Prof. Robert Aronson - tape #2 (7/10/1990) (Box 3.4)
- Prof. Robert Aronson - tape #1 (7/10/1990) (Box 3.5)
- Prof. Robert Aronson - tape #2 (7/10/1990) (Box 3.6)
- Isadore Blumen - tape #1 (Box 4.1)
  - Isadore Blumen (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - tape #1-#2 (2 cassettes)
- Isadore Blumen - tape #2 (Box 4.2)
- George Brooks (7/13/1991) (Box 5)
  - George Brooks (7/13/1991) (Box 5, Folder 1)
- M. Gardner Clark - tape #1 (7/13/1991) (Box 6.1)
  - M. Gardner Clark, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - tape #1-#2 (7/13/1991) (2 cassettes)
- M. Gardner Clark - tape #2 (7/13/1991) (Box 6.2)
- Alice Cook - tape #1 (7/13/1989) (Box 7.1)
  - Alice Cook (7/13/1989) (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Alice Cook - tape #2 (7/13/1989) (Box 7.2)
- Alice Cook - tape #1 (7/19/1989) (Box 8.1)
  - Alice Cook (7/19/1989) (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Alice Cook - tape #2 (7/19/1989) (Box 8.2)
- Donald Cullen (7/10/1990) (Box 9.1)
  - Donald Cullen (7/10/1990) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    (3 cassettes)
- Donald Cullen (7/10/1990) (Box 9.2)
- Donald Cullen (7/10/1990) (Box 9.3)
- Prof. Ronald Donovan - tape #1 (7/12/1990) (Box 10.1)
  - Prof. Ronald Donovan, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - tape #1-#2 (7/12/1990) (6 cassettes)
- Prof. Ronald Donovan - tape #2 (7/12/1990) (Box 10.2)
- Prof. Ronald Donovan - tape #1 (7/12/1990) (Box 10.3)
- Prof. Ronald Donovan - tape #2 (7/12/1990) (Box 10.4)
- Prof. Ronald Donovan - tape #1 (7/12/1990) (Box 10.5)
- Prof. Ronald Donovan - tape #2 (7/12/1990) (Box 10.6)
- Lois Gray (Box 11)
  - Lois Gray (Box 11, Folder 1)
- George Hildebrand - tape #1 (Box 12.1)
  - George Hildebrand (Box 12, Folder 1)
- George Hildebrand - tape #2 (Box 12.2)
- Vernon Jensen - tape #1 (7/11/1990) (Box 13.1)
  - Vernon Jensen, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - tape #1-#2 (7/11/1990) (9 cassettes)
- Vernon Jensen - tape #2 (7/11/1990) (Box 13.2)
- Vernon Jensen - tape #1 (7/11/1990) (Box 13.3)
- Vernon Jensen - tape #2 (7/11/1990) (Box 13.4)
- Vernon Jensen - tape #1 (7/11/1990) (Box 13.5)
- Vernon Jensen - tape#2 (7/11/1990) (Box 13.6)
- Vernon Jensen - tape #1 (7/11/1990) (Box 13.7)
- Vernon Jensen - tape #2 (7/11/1990) (Box 13.8)
- Vernon Jensen - tape #2 (7/11/1990) (Box 13.9)
- Milton Konvitz (7/14/1989) (Box 14)
  - Milton Konvitz (7/14/1989) (Box 14, Folder 1)
- John McConnell (7/11/1990) #1 (Box 15.1)
  - John McConnell (7/11/1990) (Box 15, Folder 1)
    (6 cassettes)
- John McConnell (7/11/1990) #2 (Box 15.2)
- John McConnell (7/11/1990) #2 (Box 15.3)
- John McConnell (7/11/1990) #1 (Box 15.4)
- John McConnell (7/11/1990) #2 (Box 15.5)
- John McConnell (7/11/1990) #1 (Box 15.6)
- Duncan McIntyre (7/21/1991) (Box 16.1)
  - Duncan McIntyre (7/21/1991) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    (2 cassettes)
- Duncan McIntyre (7/21/1991) (Box 16.2)
- Jean McKelvey (6/19/1991) (Box 17.1)
  - John McKelvey (6/19/1991) (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Jean McKelvey (6/19/1991) (Box 17.2)
- Jean McKelvey (10/5/1990) (Box 18.1)
  - John McKelvey (10/5/1990) (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Jean McKelvey (10/5/1990) (Box 18.2)
- Jean McKelvey (10/5/1990) (Box 18.3)
- J. Gormerley Miller (7/11/1991) (Box 19.1)
  - J. Gormley Miller (7/11/1991) (Box 19, Folder 1)
- J. Gormerley Miller (7/11/1991) (Box 19.2)
- J. Gormerley Miller (7/11/1991) (Box 19.3)
- Maurice Neufeld (7/11/1991) (Box 20.1)
  - Maurice Neufeld (7/11/1991) (Box 20, Folder 1)
    (5 cassettes)
- Maurice Neufeld (7/11/1991) (Box 20.2)
- Maurice Neufeld (7/11/1991) (Box 20.3)
- Maurice Neufeld (7/11/1991) (Box 20.4)
- Maurice Neufeld (7/11/1991) (Box 20.5)
- Prof. Maurice Neufeld - tape #1 (7/13/1990) (Box 21.1)
  - Prof. Maurice Neufeld, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - tape #1-#3 (7/13/1990) (9 cassettes)
- Prof. Maurice Neufeld - tape #2 (7/13/1990) (Box 21.2)
- Prof. Maurice Neufeld - tape #3 (7/13/1990) (Box 21.3)
- Prof. Maurice Neufeld - tape #1 (7/13/1990) (Box 21.4)
- Prof. Maurice Neufeld - tape #2 (7/13/1990) (Box 21.5)
- Prof. Maurice Neufeld - tape #3 (7/13/1990) (Box 21.6)
- Prof. Maurice Neufeld - tape #1 (7/13/1990) (Box 21.7)
- Prof. Maurice Neufeld - tape #2 (7/13/1990) (Box 21.8)
- Prof. Maurice Neufeld - tape #3 (7/13/1990) (Box 21.9)
- William Whyte (7/16/1989) (Box 22.1)
  - William Whyte (7/16/1989) (Box 22, Folder 1)
- William Whyte (7/16/1989) (Box 22.2)
- William Whyte (7/16/1989) (Box 22.3)
- William Whyte (7/16/1989) (Box 22.4)
- William Whyte (7/16/1989) (Box 22.5)
- William Whyte (7/16/1989) (Box 22.6)
- John P. Windmuller (7/20/1989) (Box 23)
  - John P. Windmuller (7/20/1989) (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Prof. Robert Raimon (7/9/1990) (Box 24.1)
  - Prof. Robert Raimon (7/9/1990) (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Prof. Robert Raimon (7/9/1990) (Box 24.2)
- Robert Raimon (7/9/1990) (Box 24.2)
- Prof. Robert Raimon (7/9/1990) (Box 24.3)
- Audio digitized from the collection. (Box 25)